[{"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "131217pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "IN", "POS", "JJ", "DT", "RB", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 16, "question": "How are you?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "VBP", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 17, "answer": "Well, that's such a lovely introduction.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "131217pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "IN", "RB", "JJ", "IN", "PRP", "VBZ", "RB", "VBN", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 37, "question": "I suppose the obvious question to -- the obvious question to that is it a white or black Santa Claus given all the controversy at the moment?", "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "TO", ":", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "TO", "DT", "VBZ", "PRP", "DT", "JJ", "CC", "JJ", "NNP", "NNP", "RB", "DT", "DT", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 38, "answer": "You know, I find that so sad that it has now become a racial question.", "question_ne_tagged": {"LOCATION": ["Santa Claus"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "131217pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "TO", "VB", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 44, "question": "Where are you going?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "VBP", "PRP", "VBG", "."], "aSentId": 45, "answer": "Well, you have to go sometime.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "131217pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "VBZ", "PRP$", "JJ", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 62, "question": "Who do you think is the most controversial entries?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "VBZ", "DT", "RBS", "JJ", "NNS", "."], "aSentId": 63, "answer": "This is our 21st year.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Miley Cyrus"]}, "docId": "131217pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "NNP", "NNP", "."], "qSentId": 72, "question": "Miley Cyrus, you know, Miley Cyrus and the tongue?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "NNP", "NNP", "CC", "DT", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 73, "answer": "I like Miley Cyrus.", "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Miley Cyrus", "Miley Cyrus"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "131217pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["IN", "PRP", "VBP", "VBN", "IN", "PRP", "TO", "DT", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 109, "question": "Why is he struggling so much to really fulfill the great flame of ambition and excitement that he was elected on originally in 2009?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "VBZ", "PRP", "VBG", "RB", "RB", "TO", "RB", "RB", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "IN", "NN", "CC", "NN", "IN", "PRP", "VBD", "VBN", "IN", "RB", "IN", "CD", "."], "aSentId": 110, "answer": "While you've touched on it to a degree.", "question_ne_tagged": {"DATE": ["2009"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "131217pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "IN", "WP", "VBZ", "RB", "VBG", "CC", "PRP", "VBZ", "IN", "WP", "NN", "PRP", "VBP", "IN", "."], "qSentId": 136, "question": "Do you think he's a hero or a villain or a bit of both?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "VBZ", "DT", "NN", "CC", "DT", "NN", "CC", "DT", "NN", "IN", "DT", "."], "aSentId": 137, "answer": "Well, you know, that what's so fascinating and it depends on what side you're on.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "131217pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "RP", "IN", "RB", "IN", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "VBN", "TO", "VB", "VBN", "DT", "NN", ",", "PRP", "VBZ", "RB", "VBN", "DT", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 173, "question": "What do you make of him?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "IN", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 174, "answer": "Well, I should point out that much as we would have loved to have interviewed the pope, he has not done an interview.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"ORGANIZATION": ["Catholic Church"]}, "docId": "131217pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBZ", "DT", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NNS", "IN", "DT", "NNP", "NNP", "."], "qSentId": 184, "question": "Is that a sign you think of a whole new papacy, a whole new Catholic church going forward?", "question_pos_tagged": ["VBZ", "IN", "DT", "NN", "PRP", "VBP", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "JJ", "NN", ",", "DT", "JJ", "JJ", "NNP", "NN", "VBG", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 185, "answer": "It's a sign of some changes in the Catholic Church.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "131217pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["RB", "."], "qSentId": 200, "question": "She's an absolute breath of fresh air, isn't she?", "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBZ", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "IN", "JJ", "NN", ",", "VBZ", "RB", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 201, "answer": "Absolutely.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "131217pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "JJ", "IN", "DT", "PRP", "VBZ", "VBN", ",", "``", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VB", "WP", "POS", "VBG", "TO", "VB", "RP", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", ".", "''"], "qSentId": 203, "question": "What do you make of her?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "IN", "PRP$", "."], "aSentId": 204, "answer": "Well, first of all she has said, \"I don't know what's going to come out of my mouth.\"", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "131217pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "DT", "NN", "IN", "DT", "IN", "DT", "."], "qSentId": 224, "question": "They're very divisive as a couple, aren't they?", "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "RB", "JJ", "IN", "DT", "NN", ",", "VBP", "RB", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 225, "answer": "I am a fan of both of this.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "131217pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "IN", "PRP", "."], "qSentId": 241, "question": "Are you laughing with me or at me?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VBG", "IN", "PRP", "CC", "IN", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 242, "answer": "I'm with you.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "131217pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "JJ", "."], "qSentId": 254, "question": "What is your personal criteria for selection?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBZ", "PRP$", "JJ", "NNS", "IN", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 255, "answer": "Well, I like controversial.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "131217pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "."], "qSentId": 260, "question": "Can you give me even a tiny clue who's number one?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "RB", "DT", "NN", "NN", "WP", "VBZ", "NN", "CD", "."], "aSentId": 261, "answer": "No.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Hugh Jackman"]}, "docId": "131217pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", "IN", "VBD", "RB", "JJ", ",", "IN", "VBD", "RB", "JJ", "PRP", "VBP", "NNP", "NNP", "."], "qSentId": 294, "question": "What about Hugh Jackman giving you a lap dance?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "IN", "NNP", "NNP", "VBG", "PRP", "DT", "NN", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 295, "answer": "Yes that was pretty good, that was pretty good I love Hugh Jackman.", "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Hugh Jackman"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Michael Thatcher"]}, "docId": "131217pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["UH", "NN", ",", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "IN", "PRP", "VBD", "TO", "NNS", ",", "IN", ":", "CD", "JJ", "NN", "VBD", "VBN", "NNP", "NNP", "MD", "PRP", "VB", "VBN", ",", "``", "NNP", "VBN", "DT", "NN", "NN", ".", "''"], "qSentId": 301, "question": "There may have been a little fling between you, any truth in that?", "question_pos_tagged": ["EX", "MD", "VB", "VBN", "DT", "RB", "VBG", "IN", "PRP", ",", "DT", "NN", "IN", "DT", "."], "aSentId": 302, "answer": "Oh please, you know, as I said to people, if -- (inaudible) had interviewed Michael Thatcher would you have said, \"Have seen this hanky panky?\"", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "131217pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": [":", "NNS", "PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "NN", ",", "NN", ",", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 311, "question": "... why did I do that?", "question_pos_tagged": [":", "WRB", "VBD", "PRP", "VBP", "IN", "."], "aSentId": 312, "answer": "... yes I mean I do, shoulda, coulda, woulda.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Elizabeth"]}, "docId": "131217pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "NNP", "VBZ", "RB", "VBN", "DT", "NN", ",", "NNP", "NNP", "VBZ", "RB", "VBN", "DT", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 323, "question": "Number five, who would you most like to interview, you've never been able to get to?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "CD", ",", "WP", "MD", "PRP", "RBS", "IN", "TO", "VB", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VBN", "JJ", "TO", "VB", "TO", "."], "aSentId": 324, "answer": "The Pope has never done an interview, Queen Elizabeth has never done an interview.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Jennifer Lawrence"]}, "docId": "131217pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "NNP", "IN", "MD", "VB", "JJ", "."], "qSentId": 329, "question": "Jennifer Lawrence?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "NNP", "."], "aSentId": 330, "answer": "Jennifer Lawrence that would be nice.", "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Jennifer Lawrence"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "131217pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "RB", "VB", "WP", "PRP", "VBP", "VBG", "IN", "."], "qSentId": 337, "question": "Number seven, if you can invite three people from all the people you've interviewed to a dream dinner party, who would you go for?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "CD", ",", "IN", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "CD", "NNS", "IN", "DT", "DT", "NNS", "PRP", "VBP", "VBN", "TO", "DT", "NN", "NN", "NN", ",", "WP", "MD", "PRP", "VB", "IN", "."], "aSentId": 338, "answer": "Let me just see who we're talking about.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Clint Eastwood"]}, "docId": "131217pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "JJ", "IN", "DT", "JJS", "CC", "DT", "JJS", "IN", "DT", ",", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "DT", "NN", "IN", "PRP", "VBD", "IN", "NNP", "NNP", "."], "qSentId": 347, "question": "Who's the biggest star you've ever meet?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBZ", "DT", "JJS", "NN", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VBN", "."], "aSentId": 348, "answer": "You know I'm not good at the biggest or the worst of that, you know, I remember an interview that I did with Clint Eastwood.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "131217pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "VBZ", "DT", "JJ", ":", "PRP", "VBZ", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "IN", "PRP", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", ":"], "qSentId": 352, "question": "(Inaudible) best and worst and worst and best, if could drop in a dessert island what?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NN", "NNP", "NNP", "JJS", "CC", "JJS", "CC", "JJS", "CC", "JJS", ",", "IN", "MD", "VB", "IN", "DT", "NN", "NN", "WP", "."], "aSentId": 353, "answer": "This is a great -- it's a great question for you because you've ...", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "131217pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["RB", "VBZ", "NNP", "NNP", "NN", "IN", "PRP", "VBZ", "RB", ",", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "PRP", "VBZ", "RB", "JJ", "CC", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "PRP", "RP", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", "TO", "VB", "IN", "."], "qSentId": 362, "question": "And which man would you have to accompany you?", "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", "VBP", "NN", "MD", "PRP", "VB", "TO", "VB", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 363, "answer": "Beethoven's Night I guess because it's just, you know, it's so bombastic and it would get me out of my depression to hear that.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "131217pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": [":", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "RB", "RB", ":", "DT", "PRP", "RB", "VBP", "RB", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "DT", "NNP", "."], "qSentId": 367, "question": "Really?", "question_pos_tagged": ["RB", "."], "aSentId": 368, "answer": "... I would be first there -- no I never have so I would read the Bible.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "131217pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VB", "EX", "MD", "VB", "DT", "NN", "WP", "VBZ", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NN", ",", "IN", "POS", "WP", "NN", "TO", "NN", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 382, "question": "Who is the one you would most like to run the country in perpetuity?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBZ", "DT", "CD", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "IN", "TO", "VB", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 383, "answer": "I don't think there should be any president who runs the country in perpetuity, that's what someone to fool about our government.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "131217pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "RB", "VBP", "RB", "VB", "DT", "NN", "WRB", "."], "qSentId": 425, "question": "Do have any explanation for why your daughter just had her tonsils out and now laying in this terrible condition?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "VBP", "DT", "NN", "IN", "WRB", "PRP$", "NN", "RB", "VBD", "PRP", "VBZ", "RP", "CC", "RB", "VBG", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 426, "answer": "I really don't know the reason why.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "131217pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "IN", "DT", "NN", ",", "PRP$", "NN", "VBZ", "RB", "JJ", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "RB", "VB", "IN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 442, "question": "What would you say as a family to that?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "MD", "PRP", "VB", "IN", "DT", "NN", "TO", "DT", "."], "aSentId": 443, "answer": "Well, as a family, our faith is so strong that we don't even think about the possibility of death.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Jahi"]}, "docId": "131217pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "JJ", ",", "PRP", "VBZ", "JJ", "TO", "VB", "IN", "NNP", "VBZ", "DT", "NN", "RB", "NN", "CC", "IN", "VBZ", "NN", "WP", "VBZ", "VBN", "VBG", "DT", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 450, "question": "What is the legal position in terms of who has the final say of what happens now to Jahi?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBZ", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "IN", "NNS", "IN", "WP", "VBZ", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "IN", "WP", "NNS", "RB", "TO", "NNP", "."], "aSentId": 451, "answer": "Well, I think first, it's important to know that Jahi is a person not evidence and that's part what's been troubling the family.", "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Jahi?"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "131217pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "WRB", "PRP", "VBP", "VBN", "PRP$", "NN", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "PRP$", "NN", "CC", "VBP", "PRP", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", "CC", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "PRP", "."], "qSentId": 464, "question": "ORGAN: Are you seeing any sign, Nailah, that she is aware of what is happening or can hear you or is reacting in any way which might suggest that she is not as the hospital believe brain dead?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ":", "NNP", "PRP", "VBG", "DT", "NN", ",", "NNP", ",", "IN", "PRP", "VBZ", "JJ", "IN", "WP", "VBZ", "VBG", "CC", "MD", "VB", "PRP", "CC", "VBZ", "VBG", "IN", "DT", "NN", "WDT", "MD", "VB", "IN", "PRP", "VBZ", "RB", "IN", "DT", "NN", "VBP", "NN", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 465, "answer": "Well, I know when I've touched her feet I can take my fingernail and run it up her feet and she'll move them.", "question_ne_tagged": {"LOCATION": ["Nailah"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "131217pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "NNP", "PRP", "VBZ", "RB", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 483, "question": "How do we -- how does it get resolved?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "VBP", "PRP", ":", "WRB", "VBZ", "PRP", "VB", "VBN", "."], "aSentId": 484, "answer": "Well, Piers it's just an awful tragic situation.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "131217pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "DT", "RB", "JJ", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "IN", "NN", "IN", "PRP", "NNPS", "."], "qSentId": 516, "question": "How are you Ms. Coulter?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "VBP", "PRP", "NNP", "NNP", "."], "aSentId": 517, "answer": "Well, I'm a little tufty that I'm not in studio with you Piers.", "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Ms. Coulter"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"ORGANIZATION": ["Piers"]}, "docId": "131217pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBZ", "DT", "NN", "NNP", "."], "qSentId": 526, "question": "What is that mean?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBZ", "IN", "JJ", "."], "aSentId": 527, "answer": "It's a joke Piers.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "131217pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "PRP", "VBZ", "JJ", "."], "qSentId": 554, "question": "So, you would say unequivocally, Jesus Christ was White as well?", "question_pos_tagged": ["IN", ",", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "RB", ",", "NNP", "NNP", "VBD", "NNP", "IN", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 555, "answer": "Well, I'd say he's Jewish.", "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Jesus Christ"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "131217pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 557, "question": "Well, is he white?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "VBZ", "PRP", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 558, "answer": "The fact.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "131217pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "RB", "VBD", "PRP", "."], "qSentId": 559, "question": "Was he white?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VBD", "."], "aSentId": 560, "answer": "I just said it.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "131217pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "VBZ", "DT", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 567, "question": "Oh is he White?", "question_pos_tagged": ["UH", "VBZ", "PRP", "NNP", "."], "aSentId": 568, "answer": "That's a fact.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "131217pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "RB", "VBD", "PRP", "."], "qSentId": 569, "question": "Was he White?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "NNP", "."], "aSentId": 570, "answer": "I just said it.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "131217pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", ":"], "qSentId": 574, "question": "But was he white?", "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", "VBD", "PRP", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 575, "answer": "Well, I don't --", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "131217pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "VBP", "JJ", "."], "qSentId": 580, "question": "(inaudible) do you feel uncomfortable with this debate?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NN", "JJ", "NN", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "JJ", "IN", "DT", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 581, "answer": "No, I think you're mad.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"LOCATION": ["Rush Limbaugh"]}, "docId": "131217pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "RB", "JJ", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "IN", "NNP", "NNP", "POS", "NN", ",", "PRP", "IN", "NN", "NN", "PRP", "VBZ", "DT", "NNP", "."], "qSentId": 591, "question": "Why would this embrace the likes of Rush Limbaugh?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "MD", "DT", "NN", "DT", "NNS", "IN", "NNP", "NNP", "."], "aSentId": 592, "answer": "I'm not sure, I mean in Rush Limbaugh's case, we of course think he is the Pope.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "131217pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "RB", "IN", "IN", "NNP", ",", "NNS", "VBP", "VBG", "PRP$", "NN", "NN", "CC", "PRP$", "NN", "NNS", "VBP", "VBG", "RP", "."], "qSentId": 612, "question": "What is going on here and how does it end?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBZ", "VBG", "IN", "RB", "CC", "WRB", "VBZ", "PRP", "VB", "."], "aSentId": 613, "answer": "I think it manifestly because of ObamaCare, people are loosing their health insurance and their health premiums are going up.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "131217pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "DT", "NN", "WP", "MD", "VB", "PRP", "."], "qSentId": 630, "question": "What doing you think are going to be the key moments now in the next couple of years which can determine what type of republican candidate faces the final run off and who might win it?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBG", "PRP", "VBP", "VBP", "VBG", "TO", "VB", "DT", "JJ", "NNS", "RB", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "IN", "NNS", "WDT", "MD", "VB", "WP", "NN", "IN", "JJ", "NN", "NNS", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "IN", "CC", "WP", "MD", "VB", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 631, "answer": "I have no idea who might win it.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "131217pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "IN", "PRP", "VBD", "CC", "RB", "PRP", "VBD", "VBN", "."], "qSentId": 642, "question": "Have you intend to get down there and buy a ticket?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VBP", "TO", "VB", "IN", "EX", "CC", "VB", "DT", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 643, "answer": "Well, if I had and then I had won.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}]